<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Moon Wolf]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Moon Wolf]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/moon-wolf/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 04:04:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/moon-wolf/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://content.bandzoogle.com/users/MoonWolf/images/content/10sTosscrop-300.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/moon-wolf/cceda599-9823-4962-9161-2fc70ead8aa4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cceda599-9823-4962-9161-2fc70ead8aa4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 21:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Producer, DJ, and multi-instrumentalist, Doug $ (dɪə'neəer-əʊ) took a break from his roots in classical music to build a career in marketing, working with some of the world's top brands, including Warner Bros. and adidas. When he returned to music, he approached it in a completely new way. Moon Wolf was launched as a solo experiment and has evolved from pop/rock into a genre-bent, eclectic, indie-pop/dance sound.  $'s lyrics are an extension of his worldview and meant to provoke thought, if not social change through positive action. “I think we have not just an opportunity, but a responsibility, to make the world around us a better place,” he says. “I try to stay focused on the moment – highs and lows – and do the best I can to respond in a positive manner. The power of our choices can be intoxicating and devastating. That's a huge part of what inspires my music.”  iOS devices and apps play a central role in Moon Wolf live performances. Motivated by necessity, $ quickly embraced the distinctive nature of this developing technology, which empowers a mix of semi-acoustic, live looping, sequenced arrangements and DJ sets. Furthermore, the live set is scalable and adaptable to each situation, making every performance unique.  A cosmic energy source that most often manifests itself in the shape of a wolf, and frequently appears in the heavens, is the inspiration behind the name.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.moonwolf.us/about</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba8fe2d-cd2f-43d4-b8c0-9c69c0f4529b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 04:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>